I want you to roll it over and look at
the
[Music]
bottom
hey dude I know who said that Austin
Nome there you go hey I left the first
message on the blue build on the bottom
of the bumper if Patrick Ain painting
hell no Patrick ain't painting he just
brought that up from the shop and
dropped it off Austin knew some what do
you think Tim looks
heavy it's actually lighter than I
so I didn't want to put too much weight
on
that why Alice got plenty of weight on
there and it just fine listen I can't
watch that without that mask no my
special sunglasses W do it only if you
got them
from
that in between here that to here bar
run off the back side of this it ain't
going to go nowhere I love this thing C
that's awesome is it
him
oh you did
it it's not
[Music]
moving you did it
again
[Music]
storage